Guide to the Washington Area Women's Center records, 1868-1989 MS2344
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Graphics, 1973-1982; Series 8
  - Thursday night music. Nov. 17. [circa 1977.] Casse Culver, Sweet Honey in the Rock, Earth Magic at Club Madame. On white posterboard., Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Two black and white copy prints from Washington Star, one of woman (Gerri ?) in WAWC early office and one of auto workshop with four women looking into engine. [On back Gerri, 197?.], Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Two black and white photographs, one outdoors with two women and other is a group. Red frames., Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Two color photographs in mat, outdoors. No identification. [on back: 82-0028 and 82-0029. Kodak print dates are Oct 1978 and Nov 1978., 1978 October-November; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Two color photographs of two women behind WAWC informational table in front of WAWC banner, outside with several women and one child in front., Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Two color sheets with black and white photo negatives, some are loose., Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Two young women weaving in black and white photograph. Signature of McPowell. [On back: 82-0019- same number as Women in Gear.], Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Wall Flower Order dance collective, Dec. 12, GWU, 1970. On back: 82-0057., 1970 December 12; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Wall label states: Women's Visions photography contest winners"., Undated; Series 8 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - WAWC Women's Nite Out, September 8 and 22, October 6. undated mock up. Performers include Wendy Stevens, Carol Anne Douglas and Susan Wood-Thompson., Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Wilson Center, Fundraising Benefit for Fields of Plenty. [in English & Spanish] Sunday, January 23rd [no year]. Performers include Lucha, Rumisongos, Sweey Honey in the Rock and Hysteria. Poster., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Women I Have Known or Visioned by Lauren Weil. Art on the Walls, Washington Womens [sic] Center, March 27 to April 29, 1977., Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Women in Gear, seven black and white photos and one color photo by Fran Lynch. [On backs: 82-0019 to 82-0024 (2), 82-0026 to 82-0030. Missing 82-0028 and 82-0029.] Incudes handwritten exhibit wall label., Undated; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Women's Strike demonstration, August 26, 1970, NY City. Black and white photo by Diana Davies., 1970 August 26; Series 8 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Susan B. Anthony 1870. "So while I do not pray for anybody,…" Large silkscreen poster. On back: 82-0045., Undated; Series 8 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - WAWC Income & Expense Pie Chart, Jan 1981 to Oct 1981. Rolled up poster, damaged., 1981 January-October; Series 8 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Willie Tyson, "Debutante". Album info plus photo, publicity, all songs, 1977. Rolled up poster., Series 8 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Working Women Unite. Photo of two women hugging, sitting down. Large silkscreen poster. [no date], Undated; Series 8 (Oversize-folder 1)
- Unsorted documents, circa 1970 - circa 1987; Series 9; 8.5 Linear Feet
  Arranged in no particular order, but maintained in the order (per box) that existed when donated.
  This unprocessed series contains newsletters, fliers, correspondence, meeting minutes, financial records and brochures. These records cover the date range circa 1970 - circa 1987.
  - Incorporation, 1973-1976; Series 9 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    papers filed with the Recorder of Deeds including articles of incorporation, by-laws, annual reports: 1973-1976, petition for reinstatement of incorporation 11/8/76, and change of registered agent 11/4/76.
  - Financial tax records, 1976-1982; Series 9 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Paid invoices, 1976; Series 9 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - WAWC tax information, 1977; Series 9 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Taxes, 1979; Series 9 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Financial records, 1979-1982; Series 9 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Tax information, 1976; Series 9 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Financial records, 1981; Series 9 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - P. Street festival, 1981; Series 9 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Tax materials, 1982-1983; Series 9 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Financial bank records [1/2], 1983-1987; Series 9 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Financial bank records [2/2], 1983-1987; Series 9 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Lesbian Youth Outreach LYO, 1984; Series 9 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Financial records, 1984-1986; Series 9 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Certificate and articles of incorporation, 1984 September 4; Series 9 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Financial records, 1986-1987; Series 9 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - June Moon Cruise, 1982; Series 9 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Archives periodical catalog [1/4], undated; Series 9 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Archives periodical catalog [2/4], undated; Series 9 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Archives periodical catalog [3/4], undated; Series 9 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Archives periodical catalog [4/4], undated; Series 9 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters, brochures, and fliers unsorted, 1980-1983; Series 9 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Newsletters, brochures, fliers unsorted, 1969-1984; Series 9 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, brochures, fliers unsorted, circa 1980s; Series 9 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, brochures, fliers unsorted, circa 1980s; Series 9 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters, brochures, fliers unsorted, circa 1980s; Series 9 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, brochures, fliers unsorted, circa 1980s; Series 9 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Newsletters, brochures, fliers unsorted, circa 1980s; Series 9 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, brochures, fliers unsorted, circa 1980s; Series 9 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Newsletters, brochures, fliers unsorted, circa 1980s; Series 9 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Unfiled loose papers in Quest box, 1973-1979; Series 9 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Rejected manuscripts A-L, circa 1977; Series 9 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Rejected manuscripts M-W, circa 1977; Series 9 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Ourstory Herstory a working paper on the DC women's Liberation movement 1968-1971, 1971 May 21; Series 9 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Historical records [1/9], circa 1980; Series 9 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Historical records [2/9], circa 1980; Series 9 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Historical records [3/9], circa 1980; Series 9 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Historical records [4/9], circa 1980; Series 9 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Historical records [6/9], circa 1980; Series 9 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Historical records [7/9], circa 1980; Series 9 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Historical records [8/9], circa 1980; Series 9 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Historical records [9/9], circa 1980; Series 9 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Information cards A-E [1/3], undated; Series 9 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Information cards F-O [2/3], undated; Series 9 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Information cards O-Z [3/3], undated; Series 9 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Information resources, undated; Series 9 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Information index cards [1/5], undated; Series 9 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Information index cards [2/5], undated; Series 9 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Information index cards [3/5], undated; Series 9 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Information index cards [4/5], undated; Series 9 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Information index cards [5/5], undated; Series 9 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Ephemera [buttons, bumper sticker], undated; Series 9 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - WAWC minutes, 1982; Series 9 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - WAWC phone/mail log [1/2], 1982; Series 9 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - WAWC phone/mail log [2/2], 1982; Series 9 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1982; Series 9 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - WAWC space book, reservations, calendar papers, 1982; Series 9 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - WAWC records, 1982; Series 9 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - WAWC area groups, 1982; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - WAWC materials groups, 1982; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - WAWC loose early records [1/2], 1972-1981; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - WAWC loose early records [2/2], 1972-1981; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - WAWC mailing lists, 1972; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - WAWC serach committee questionnaire, 1983; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Art on wall, 1982; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - WAWC records, 1980-1981; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - WAWC staff member's personal notes, undated; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Recorder of deeds, annual report, certificate of incorporation, 1972-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Loose papers [1/4], circa 1970s; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Loose papers [2/4], circa 1970s; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Loose papers [3/4], circa 1970s; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Loose papers [4/4], circa 1970s; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Gay Pride DC, 1980; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - DC Commission for Women, 1980; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Loose papers [1/5], circa 1976-1981; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Loose papers [2/5], circa 1976-1981; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Loose papers [3/5], circa 1976-1981; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Loose papers [4/5], circa 1976-1981; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Loose papers [5/5], circa 1976-1981; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - WAWC publicity/outreach, 1980; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - WAWC log books, 1979; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - WAWC notes from management workshop, 1977; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Loose papers [1/3], circa 1970-1980s; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Loose papers [2/3], circa 1970-1980s; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Loose papers [3/3], circa 1970-1980s; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - WAWC early records, circa 1980s; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - WAWC office coordination book, 1974; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Quest a feminist quarterly, 1980; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Quest, 1974; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Quest advertising inquiries and correspondence, undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - able to choose? by Marlene Wills, 1981; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - DC Area Feminist Alliance, 1978; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Quest correspondence, 1978-1979; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Quest Ads Mother Jones, 1975-1976; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Loose papers [1/4], 1978-1980; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Loose papers [2/4], 1972-1984; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Loose papers [3/4], 1973-1979; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Loose papers [4/4], 1977-1979; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - WAWC early records, 1974-1975; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    includes Board meeting minutes
  - Early history [1/3], 1979-1980; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    folder contains records of the Feminist Anti-Nuclear Task Force and Quest
  - Early history [2/3], 1978-1979; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Early history [3/3], 1979; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - WAWC newsletter, 1980 June; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - WAWC early records, 1978-1982; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    Folder contains materials related to the DC Area Feminist Alliance
  - Training manual / brochure, undated; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Women's Center rap group, undated; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - WAWC graphic arts, undated; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - N.L. orig. manuscripts to be stored for archives [1/3], 1979; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - N.L. orig. manuscripts to be stored for archives [2/3], 1979; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - N.L. orig. manuscripts to be stored for archives [3/3], 1979; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - WAWC office log, 1980-1981; Series 9 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - WAWC records, 1978-1980; Series 9 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Funding, circa 1977; Series 9 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - WAWC staff phone/mail log, 1981; Series 9 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - WAWC papers, undated; Series 9 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - WAWC public relations, Susanna Sturgis, 1978; Series 9 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - WAWC newsletter, Susanna Sturgis, undated; Series 9 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Resource material and groups on proposal writing, 1971-1975; Series 9 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Resource material on foundations and funding, 1972; Series 9 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Fundraising, 1971-1980; Series 9 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Funding, 1977; Series 9 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Proposals for funding, 1983; Series 9 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - WAWC records, 1987-1988; Series 9 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Promotional flyers, undated; Series 9 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - WAWC Federal excempt status, 1975; Series 9 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Financial records, 1974-1975; Series 9 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Article by Maria Tabor, undated; Series 9 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Sojourner Truth Women's School, undated; Series 9 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Sojourner Truth Women's School, 1981; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Sojourner Truth Women's School on-site registration informational materials, undated; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Sojourner Truth Women's School registration materials, 1980 Fall; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Sojourner Truth Women's School booklet, 1980-1981; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Sojourner Truth Women's School, 1980; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - WAWC 1975 Christmas party show, Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - National Association of Women's Centers (NAWC), 1986-1987; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - NAWC handwritten notes (mostly Angie Carrera), undated; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - NAWC minutes, 1986; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - NAWC membership lists, undated; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - NAWC surveys, undated; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - NAWC communication, 1985-1986; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 12)